http://www.projectspace.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
At ProjectSpace we respect your right to privacy and we understand that, as a visitor to ProjectSpace.com, you prefer to control your own personal information and preferences. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information and preferences when you visit certain areas of ProjectSpace.com, request information, or subscribe to ProjectSpace newsletters.
We will guard the personal information you share with us to ensure the content and services that we provide on ProjectSpace.com (and related ProjectSpace sites) are always tailored to your current, designated preferences.
When you provide ProjectSpace with your name (or alias), e-mail address, mailing address, or telephone number, and you "opt in," ProjectSpace and ProjectSpace representatives may use the provided information to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, training, new services, and other ProjectSpace related information. ("Representatives" include value-added resellers and authorized training partners.) ProjectSpace does not offer, or allow the selling of, any user-provided information to third parties.
ProjectSpace respects the rights users give us when opting to receive e-mail communications and enforces internal policies to preserve those rights. It is our objective to retain the long-term ability to continue to communicate with our users.
If you do not want ProjectSpace or ProjectSpace representatives to contact you, you may "opt out" of this preference at any time, whether you're online or contacting ProjectSpace directly. As part of your preference flexibility, you'll always have the option to opt back in and have ProjectSpace contact you based on your previous or new preferences. For instructions, please see the section "Contact Us," below.
ProjectSpace and the use of log files (cookies)
ProjectSpace offers a service to all ProjectSpace.com visitors. In order to establish a service, visitors are requested to provide both personal information and preferences. This information is stored and protected by your user-established User ID and Password.
No information, other than that found in the cookie, will be accessed by any ProjectSpace system. Access to your ProjectSpace information always requires both your User ID and Password.
ProjectSpace also utilizes visitor log files (cookies) with our Web site. Once a user enters our site, a cookie follows them through their click stream path. Examples of information being collected by these cookies include the number of times a user came to our site(s), and the paths they took to get there. And the path through the application for an auditing trail.
ProjectSpace uses the data collected from Web site visitor cookies in aggregate form only and does not collect any personally identifiable information. Use of this information helps us better understand what users are seeking and learning at our Web site(s) and helps us identify potential navigation issues.
How ProjectSpace will protect your personal information
ProjectSpace will always protect the personal information that you share with us. ProjectSpace stores information internally in a controlled, secure environment. If, for example, you make a purchase online, we route all transactions through SSL (Secure Socket Layers) and will process your credit card number only to secure your current payment. The SSL transaction does not retain your credit card number subsequent to the transaction at hand and will not use the number for marketing purposes.
ProjectSpace may occasionally present a special contest or promotion that is sponsored by another company. To qualify for entry, we may ask you to provide personal information. If we plan to share that information with the sponsor(s), we will provide an up-front statement to that effect.
At ProjectSpace the most important thing for us is that you make the choice that is best for you.
Contact Us:
E-MAIL:
rhorton (a) ProjectSpace.com
POSTAL MAIL:
ProjectSpace, LLC.
Attn: Privacy
23 Lakeview Dr.
Canfield, Ohio 44406USA
